{"Topic": "Asian Games (updated)", "Subject": "General Knowledge", "Data": [{"Question": "In which city have the Asian Games been held the most number of times?", "op1": "New Delhi", "op2": "Tokyo", "op3": "Bangkok", "op4": "Seoul", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "In which year were the Asian Games held for the first time?", "op1": "1936", "op2": "1982", "op3": "1951", "op4": "1948", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "How many times have the Asian Games been held in South Korea?", "op1": "2", "op2": "1", "op3": "4", "op4": "3", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "Where were the 2018 Asian Games held?", "op1": "Manila", "op2": "Doha", "op3": "Bangkok", "op4": "Jakarta", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "Where are the headquarters of Olympic Council of Asia, the body which organises the Asian Games, located?", "op1": "Beijing", "op2": "New Delhi", "op3": "Tokyo", "op4": "Kuwait City", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "Who of the following is the first Indian woman to win a gold medal at the Asian Games?", "op1": "PT Usha", "op2": "Karnam Malleshwari", "op3": "Kamaljit Sandhu", "op4": "Sania Mirza", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "How many times has India won the gold medal in men's hockey at the Asian Games?", "op1": "Two", "op2": "Three", "op3": "Four", "op4": "Five", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "What has been highest rank of India in the medals tally at the Asian Games since their beginning in 1951?", "op1": "First", "op2": "Second", "op3": "Third", "op4": "Fourth", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Which Indian athlete holds the Asian Games record for 1500 m race that she established in 2002?", "op1": "PT Usha", "op2": "Tintu Luka", "op3": "Sunita Rani", "op4": "Shiny Abraham", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "How many countries participated at the 2018 Asian Games?", "op1": "45", "op2": "51", "op3": "42", "op4": "37", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "What kind of animal is Bhin Bhin in the official mascot of the 2018 Asian Games?", "op1": "Greater Bird of Paradise", "op2": "Rhinoceros", "op3": "Deer", "op4": "Komodo Dragon", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "In which province of Indonesia is the city of Palembang, which co-hosted the games located?", "op1": "South Sumatra", "op2": "West Sumatra", "op3": "East Java", "op4": "Central Java", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "From which city did the torch relay for the 2018 Asian Games begin on 15 July 2018?", "op1": "Incheon", "op2": "Hangzhou", "op3": "New Delhi", "op4": "Olympia", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "Which country sent the most number of athletes to the 2018 Asian Games?", "op1": "China", "op2": "Japan", "op3": "South Korea", "op4": "Indonesia", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "In which event did India win the maximum number of medals at the 2018 Asian Games?", "op1": "Shooting", "op2": "Athletics", "op3": "Archery", "op4": "Boxing", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Which team won the gold medal in men's Kabaddi at the 2018 Asian Games?", "op1": "Iran", "op2": "South Korea", "op3": "India", "op4": "Bangladesh", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "The Most Valuable Player award at the 2018 Asian Games has been given to -", "op1": "Li Bingjie", "op2": "Rikako Ikee", "op3": "Li Yue", "op4": "Yukiko Ueno", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Which country won the gold medal in men's hockey at the 2018 Asian Games?", "op1": "South Korea", "op2": "Japan", "op3": "Pakistan", "op4": "Malaysia", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Who was the flag bearer of the Indian contingent at the opening ceremony of Asian Games 2018?", "op1": "Saina Nehwal", "op2": "Neeraj Chopra", "op3": "PV Sindhu", "op4": "Bajrang Poonia", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Who was the flag bearer of the Indian contingent at the closing ceremony of Asian Games 2018?", "op1": "Rani Rampal", "op2": "Rahi Sarnobat", "op3": "Swapna Barman", "op4": "Hima Das", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "What was the rank of India in the final medals tally at the 2018 Asian Games?", "op1": "Fifth", "op2": "Sixth", "op3": "Seventh", "op4": "Eighth", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "In which event did Tejinderpal Singh Toor set a games record at the 2018 Asian Games?", "op1": "Javelin Throw", "op2": "Shot Put", "op3": "Discus", "op4": "Hammer Throw", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "To which team did Indian women's hockey team lose in the finals to win the silver at the 2018 Asian Games?", "op1": "Japan", "op2": "South Korea", "op3": "Malaysia", "op4": "Indonesia", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "PV Sindhu lost to Tai Tzu Ying in the finals at the 2018 Asian Games. To which country does Tai Tzu Ying belong?", "op1": "Japan", "op2": "China", "op3": "South Korea", "op4": "Chinese Taipei", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "Which city in China will be the host for 2022 Asian Games?", "op1": "Shanghai", "op2": "Guangzhou", "op3": "Hangzhou", "op4": "Shenzhen", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "Who of the following became the first Indian to win a gold medal in women's heptathlon at the Asian Games?", "op1": "Swapna Barman", "op2": "Dutee Chand", "op3": "Hima Das", "op4": "Sudha Singh", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Which of the following was the motto of the 2018 Asian Games?", "op1": "Games for Peace", "op2": "Energy of Asia", "op3": "Light of Asia", "op4": "To the world, with love", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Which of the following is the medals tally in gold, silver, bronze order of India at the 2018 Asian Games?", "op1": "15, 24, 30", "op2": "14, 25, 30", "op3": "15, 23, 31", "op4": "14, 22, 35", "Answer": 1}]}